export const easy = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the cowboy in Toy Story?",
    answers: ["Buzz", "Woody", "Jessie", "Rex"],
    correct_answer: "Woody",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which movie features the song 'Hakuna Matata'?",
    answers: ["Aladdin", "The Lion King", "Mulan", "Beauty and the Beast"],
    correct_answer: "The Lion King",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who is the main character in the movie 'Finding Nemo'?",
    answers: ["Dory", "Bruce", "Marlin", "Nemo"],
    correct_answer: "Nemo",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "In 'The Lion King', what kind of animal is Timon?",
    answers: ["Lion", "Hyena", "Warthog", "Meerkat"],
    correct_answer: "Meerkat",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a song called 'A Whole New World'?",
    answers: [
      "Pocahontas",
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "The Little Mermaid",
      "Aladdin",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Aladdin",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the princess in 'Sleeping Beauty'?",
    answers: ["Aurora", "Ariel", "Jasmine", "Belle"],
    correct_answer: "Aurora",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "In which movie does a flying house get carried away by balloons?",
    answers: ["Toy Story", "Up", "Frozen", "Moana"],
    correct_answer: "Up",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the name of the snowman in 'Frozen'?",
    answers: ["Kristoff", "Hans", "Sven", "Olaf"],
    correct_answer: "Olaf",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which movie features a panda who becomes a kung fu master?",
    answers: ["Mulan", "Kung Fu Panda", "Shrek", "How to Train Your Dragon"],
    correct_answer: "Kung Fu Panda",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "In 'Toy Story', what is the name of Buzz Lightyear's enemy?",
    answers: ["Sid", "Woody", "Zurg", "Rex"],
    correct_answer: "Zurg",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Who is the main character in the movie 'Shrek'?",
    answers: ["Fiona", "Lord Farquaad", "Shrek", "Donkey"],
    correct_answer: "Shrek",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Which Disney movie features the character 'Simba'?",
    answers: ["Tarzan", "Mulan", "Aladdin", "The Lion King"],
    correct_answer: "The Lion King",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What type of fish is Nemo?",
    answers: ["Goldfish", "Betta", "Clownfish", "Guppy"],
    correct_answer: "Clownfish",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which movie features a character named 'Buzz Lightyear'?",
    answers: ["Finding Nemo", "Toy Story", "Monsters, Inc.", "The Incredibles"],
    correct_answer: "Toy Story",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "In which movie does the character 'Elsa' appear?",
    answers: ["Tangled", "Moana", "Brave", "Frozen"],
    correct_answer: "Frozen",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "In which movie does a fish named Dory help a clownfish find his way home?",
    answers: [
      "Finding Nemo",
      "Finding Dory",
      "The Little Mermaid",
      "Toy Story",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Finding Nemo",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Lightning McQueen'?",
    answers: ["Planes", "Finding Nemo", "Toy Story", "Cars"],
    correct_answer: "Cars",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Who is the main character in 'The Lion King'?",
    answers: ["Simba", "Mufasa", "Scar", "Timon"],
    correct_answer: "Simba",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question:
      "In which movie does a young deer learn about life in the forest?",
    answers: ["Dumbo", "The Fox and the Hound", "The Jungle Book", "Bambi"],
    correct_answer: "Bambi",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question:
      "What is the name of the young girl who befriends a giant in 'The BFG'?",
    answers: ["Matilda", "Alice", "Sophie", "Lucy"],
    correct_answer: "Sophie",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Maui'?",
    answers: ["Frozen", "Moana", "Zootopia", "Tangled"],
    correct_answer: "Moana",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question:
      "In which movie does the character 'Woody' say, 'There's a snake in my boot'?",
    answers: ["The Incredibles", "Ratatouille", "Cars", "Toy Story"],
    correct_answer: "Toy Story",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Mike Wazowski'?",
    answers: ["Toy Story", "Finding Nemo", "Inside Out", "Monsters, Inc."],
    correct_answer: "Monsters, Inc.",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "What is the name of the toy spaceman in 'Toy Story'?",
    answers: ["Woody", "Mr. Potato Head", "Rex", "Buzz Lightyear"],
    correct_answer: "Buzz Lightyear",
  },

  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Which movie features the song 'Let It Go'?",
    answers: ["Zootopia", "Moana", "Frozen", "Tangled"],
    correct_answer: "Frozen",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "In which movie does a rat become a chef?",
    answers: ["The Incredibles", "Cars", "Toy Story", "Ratatouille"],
    correct_answer: "Ratatouille",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a deer named Bambi?",
    answers: ["The Fox and the Hound", "Dumbo", "Bambi", "The Jungle Book"],
    correct_answer: "Bambi",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "What is the name of the princess in 'Beauty and the Beast'?",
    answers: ["Aurora", "Jasmine", "Ariel", "Belle"],
    correct_answer: "Belle",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Hercules'?",
    answers: ["Tarzan", "Hercules", "Mulan", "Aladdin"],
    correct_answer: "Hercules",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question:
      "In which movie does a girl with long hair get locked in a tower?",
    answers: ["Frozen", "Moana", "Brave", "Tangled"],
    correct_answer: "Tangled",
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question:
      "What is the name of the lion cub who becomes king in 'The Lion King'?",
    answers: ["Simba", "Nala", "Scar", "Mufasa"],
    correct_answer: "Simba",
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "What is the name of the princess in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
    answers: ["Ariel", "Aurora", "Jasmine", "Belle"],
    correct_answer: "Ariel",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "In which Disney movie does the character 'Pocahontas' appear?",
    answers: ["Aladdin", "Pocahontas", "Mulan", "Hercules"],
    correct_answer: "Pocahontas",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who can freeze things in 'Frozen'?",
    answers: ["Olaf", "Elsa", "Anna", "Kristoff"],
    correct_answer: "Elsa",
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Pocahontas'?",
    answers: [
      "The Little Mermaid",
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "Pocahontas",
      "Mulan",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Pocahontas",
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "What is the name of the genie in 'Aladdin'?",
    answers: ["Jafar", "Abu", "Rajah", "Genie"],
    correct_answer: "Genie",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Tiana'?",
    answers: ["The Princess and the Frog", "Tangled", "Moana", "Frozen"],
    correct_answer: "The Princess and the Frog",
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "What is the name of the lion in 'The Lion King'?",
    answers: ["Scar", "Nala", "Mufasa", "Simba"],
    correct_answer: "Simba",
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "In which movie does the character 'WALL-E' appear?",
    answers: ["The Incredibles", "Toy Story", "WALL-E", "Monsters, Inc."],
    correct_answer: "WALL-E",
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question: "Which movie features the character 'Belle'?",
    answers: ["Tangled", "Frozen", "Beauty and the Beast", "Moana"],
    correct_answer: "Beauty and the Beast",
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "What is the name of the bear in The Jungle Book?",
    answers: ["Shere Khan", "Baloo", "Bagheera", "Kaa"],
    correct_answer: "Baloo",
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "Which Disney princess has a pet tiger named Rajah?",
    answers: ["Cinderella", "Mulan", "Ariel", "Jasmine"],
    correct_answer: "Jasmine",
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "In the movie Frozen, what is the name of Elsa’s younger sister?",
    answers: ["Belle", "Anna", "Tiana", "Merida"],
    correct_answer: "Anna",
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question:
      "What is the name of the fairy who helps Cinderella in the movie?",
    answers: ["Tinker Bell", "Fairy Godmother", "Maleficent", "Aurora"],
    correct_answer: "Fairy Godmother",
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question:
      "In The Little Mermaid, what is the name of Ariel’s best fish friend?",
    answers: ["Sebastian", "Eric", "Scuttle", "Flounder"],
    correct_answer: "Flounder",
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "What does Cinderella's fairy godmother turn into a carriage?",
    answers: ["An apple", "A pumpkin", "A melon", "A potato"],
    correct_answer: "A pumpkin",
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: "Which Disney movie features the song 'Be Our Guest'?",
    answers: [
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "Aladdin",
      "The Lion King",
      "The Little Mermaid",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Beauty and the Beast",
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "Who is the villain in 101 Dalmatians?",
    answers: ["Cruella de Vil", "Maleficent", "Ursula", "Jafar"],
    correct_answer: "Cruella de Vil",
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "In Moana, what is the name of Moana's pet pig?",
    answers: ["Hei Hei", "Pua", "Tui", "Maui"],
    correct_answer: "Pua",
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "What is the name of the city where The Incredibles live?",
    answers: ["Gotham", "Metropolis", "Metroville", "Zootopia"],
    correct_answer: "Metroville",
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question: "In Zootopia, what kind of animal is Judy Hopps?",
    answers: ["Fox", "Lion", "Elephant", "Rabbit"],
    correct_answer: "Rabbit",
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a magical lamp with a genie inside?",
    answers: ["The Little Mermaid", "Beauty and the Beast", "Mulan", "Aladdin"],
    correct_answer: "Aladdin",
  },
  {
    id: 53,
    question:
      "In Toy Story, what is the name of Andy's neighbor who destroys toys?",
    answers: ["Sid", "Tom", "Jerry", "Bob"],
    correct_answer: "Sid",
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    question: "What kind of animal is Simba in The Lion King?",
    answers: ["Tiger", "Lion", "Cheetah", "Leopard"],
    correct_answer: "Lion",
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    question: "Which Disney character is known for saying 'Oh, boy!'?",
    answers: ["Mickey Mouse", "Donald Duck", "Goofy", "Pluto"],
    correct_answer: "Mickey Mouse",
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a girl with long magical hair?",
    answers: ["Tangled", "Brave", "Frozen", "Moana"],
    correct_answer: "Tangled",
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    question: "What is the name of the magical flying carpet in 'Aladdin'?",
    answers: ["Enchanted Rug", "Flying Carpet", "Mystic Rug", "Magic Carpet"],
    correct_answer: "Magic Carpet",
  },
  {
    id: 58,
    question: "In The Little Mermaid, what is the name of the sea witch?",
    answers: ["Melody", "Vanessa", "Morgana", "Ursula"],
    correct_answer: "Ursula",
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    question: "What is the name of Mickey Mouse's dog?",
    answers: ["Donald", "Max", "Pluto", "Goofy"],
    correct_answer: "Pluto",
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    question: "Which Disney princess sings 'Part of Your World'?",
    answers: ["Belle", "Jasmine", "Mulan", "Ariel"],
    correct_answer: "Ariel",
  },
  {
    id: 61,
    question: "In which Disney movie does the character Maui appear?",
    answers: ["Moana", "Frozen", "Tangled", "Brave"],
    correct_answer: "Moana",
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    question:
      "Which Disney movie features a young girl who befriends a mermaid named Ariel?",
    answers: [
      "The Little Mermaid",
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "Aladdin",
      "Cinderella",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Little Mermaid",
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    question: "Who is the villain in Beauty and the Beast?",
    answers: ["Hades", "Jafar", "Gaston", "Scar"],
    correct_answer: "Gaston",
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    question: "In The Lion King, who is Simba's father?",
    answers: ["Timon", "Rafiki", "Scar", "Mufasa"],
    correct_answer: "Mufasa",
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a boy raised by wolves?",
    answers: ["Bambi", "Tarzan", "The Jungle Book", "The Lion King"],
    correct_answer: "The Jungle Book",
  },
  {
    id: 66,
    question: "What is the name of Aladdin's monkey?",
    answers: ["Rajah", "Abu", "Iago", "Genie"],
    correct_answer: "Abu",
  },

  {
    id: 67,
    question: "What is the name of the toy cowboy in 'Toy Story'?",
    answers: ["Buzz Lightyear", "Rex", "Woody", "Mr. Potato Head"],
    correct_answer: "Woody",
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    question: "Which Disney princess has a pet tiger named Rajah?",
    answers: ["Jasmine", "Ariel", "Belle", "Snow White"],
    correct_answer: "Jasmine",
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    question: "In Mulan, what is the name of Mulan's dragon companion?",
    answers: ["Mushu", "Khan", "Cri-Kee", "Shan Yu"],
    correct_answer: "Mushu",
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a villain named Hades?",
    answers: ["Hercules", "Tarzan", "The Little Mermaid", "The Lion King"],
    correct_answer: "Hercules",
  },
  {
    id: 71,
    question: "What animal is the character 'Nala' in 'The Lion King'?",
    answers: ["Elephant", "Zebra", "Lion", "Giraffe"],
    correct_answer: "Lion",
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    question: "Who is the villain in Sleeping Beauty?",
    answers: ["Maleficent", "Jafar", "Ursula", "Scar"],
    correct_answer: "Maleficent",
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    question:
      "In 'Beauty and the Beast,' what is the name of the enchanted household items?",
    answers: [
      "The Bewitched Staff",
      "The Enchanted Objects",
      "The Magic Helpers",
      "The Cursed Items",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Enchanted Objects",
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a villain named Ursula?",
    answers: [
      "The Little Mermaid",
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "Aladdin",
      "The Lion King",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Little Mermaid",
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: "In The Lion King, who is Timon's best friend?",
    answers: ["Pumbaa", "Simba", "Rafiki", "Zazu"],
    correct_answer: "Pumbaa",
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    question: "What is the name of the circus in 'Dumbo'?",
    answers: [
      "The Greatest Show",
      "The Flying Circus",
      "The Big Top",
      "WDP Circus",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Big Top",
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    question: "In Aladdin, what is the name of Jasmine's tiger?",
    answers: ["Rajah", "Abu", "Iago", "Jafar"],
    correct_answer: "Rajah",
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: "Who is the villain in The Lion King?",
    answers: ["Scar", "Mufasa", "Nala", "Zazu"],
    correct_answer: "Scar",
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    question: "In Frozen, what is the name of the reindeer?",
    answers: ["Sven", "Kristoff", "Olaf", "Hans"],
    correct_answer: "Sven",
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a girl named Rapunzel?",
    answers: ["Tangled", "Brave", "Frozen", "Moana"],
    correct_answer: "Tangled",
  },
  {
    id: 81,
    question:
      "In The Little Mermaid, what does Ariel trade to Ursula in exchange for legs?",
    answers: ["Her voice", "Her hair", "Her tail", "Her fins"],
    correct_answer: "Her voice",
  },
  {
    id: 82,
    question: "Which Disney princess has a stepmother named Lady Tremaine?",
    answers: ["Cinderella", "Ariel", "Belle", "Snow White"],
    correct_answer: "Cinderella",
  },
  {
    id: 83,
    question: "In Moana, what is the name of Moana's grandmother?",
    answers: ["Tala", "Sina", "Tui", "Maui"],
    correct_answer: "Tala",
  },
  {
    id: 84,
    question: "Which Disney movie features the song 'Let It Go'?",
    answers: ["Frozen", "Moana", "Tangled", "Brave"],
    correct_answer: "Frozen",
  },
  {
    id: 85,
    question: "What is the name of the princess in Aladdin?",
    answers: ["Jasmine", "Ariel", "Belle", "Mulan"],
    correct_answer: "Jasmine",
  },
  {
    id: 86,
    question: "In The Jungle Book, who is the villain?",
    answers: ["Shere Khan", "Baloo", "Bagheera", "Kaa"],
    correct_answer: "Shere Khan",
  },
  {
    id: 87,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a boy named Peter Pan?",
    answers: [
      "Peter Pan",
      "Cinderella",
      "Sleeping Beauty",
      "The Little Mermaid",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Peter Pan",
  },
  {
    id: 88,
    question: "In Beauty and the Beast, what is the name of the teapot?",
    answers: ["Mrs. Potts", "Lumière", "Cogsworth", "Chip"],
    correct_answer: "Mrs. Potts",
  },
  {
    id: 89,
    question: "Which Disney princess has a stepmother named Lady Tremaine?",
    answers: ["Snow White", "Ariel", "Belle", "Cinderella"],
    correct_answer: "Cinderella",
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    question: "What is the name of Simba's best friend in The Lion King?",
    answers: ["Nala", "Timon", "Pumbaa", "Rafiki"],
    correct_answer: "Nala",
  },
  {
    id: 91,
    question: "In Aladdin, what is the name of Aladdin's monkey?",
    answers: ["Iago", "Rajah", "Genie", "Abu"],
    correct_answer: "Abu",
  },
  {
    id: 92,
    question: "Who is the villain in The Little Mermaid?",
    answers: ["Sebastian", "Ursula", "Flounder", "Scuttle"],
    correct_answer: "Ursula",
  },
  {
    id: 93,
    question: "Which Disney princess has a stepmother named Lady Tremaine?",
    answers: ["Ariel", "Belle", "Snow White", "Cinderella"],
    correct_answer: "Cinderella",
  },
  {
    id: 94,
    question:
      "In Frozen, what is the name of the ice harvester who helps Anna?",
    answers: ["Hans", "Sven", "Kristoff", "Olaf"],
    correct_answer: "Kristoff",
  },
  {
    id: 95,
    question: "In Beauty and the Beast, what is the name of Belle's father?",
    answers: ["Gaston", "Lumière", "Maurice", "Cogsworth"],
    correct_answer: "Maurice",
  },
  {
    id: 96,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a girl with long magical hair?",
    answers: ["Moana", "Frozen", "Tangled", "Brave"],
    correct_answer: "Tangled",
  },
  {
    id: 97,
    question: "In Moana, what is the name of Moana's pet pig?",
    answers: ["Hei Hei", "Maui", "Tui", "Pua"],
    correct_answer: "Pua",
  },
  {
    id: 98,
    question: "In The Lion King, who is Simba's father?",
    answers: ["Scar", "Mufasa", "Timon", "Rafiki"],
    correct_answer: "Mufasa",
  },
  {
    id: 99,
    question: "Which Disney movie features a living snowman named Olaf?",
    answers: ["Tangled", "Frozen", "Brave", "Moana"],
    correct_answer: "Frozen",
  },
  {
    id: 100,
    question: "What kind of animal is Simba in The Lion King?",
    answers: ["Leopard", "Lion", "Cheetah", "Tiger"],
    correct_answer: "Lion",
  },
];
